tranceaddict.com 2014-12-03

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement for TranceAddict.com**  

TranceAddict **™** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for TranceAddict.com:

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. We use this information only for statistical purposes to find out where our visitors are coming from and to resolve disputes. If you are known to be abusing system resources and/or disrupting the overall functioning of the site then this information is used to block you and depending on severity - also notify your Internet Service Provider.

**Cookies** In order to prevent multiple pop-up advertisements from being displayed to you while surfing on TranceAddict.com a cookie is set allowing us to know that you have already seen a popup and won't have to deal with more of them when moving throughout the site.

We use various outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. In-House Banner sales are hosted by us so as to protect your privacy, browsing habits and referring URLs.   
**  
Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

**Personal Information**

Use of this web site does not require any personal information or collection any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Registration in the forums and/or the TranceAddict.com mailing list only requires that you submit your e-mail address and country of residence. These e-mail addresses are **NOT** publically accessible but keep in mind if you post your e-mail address in the a message within the forums then it may be picked up by a search engine (alternatively you can send a Private Message (via the forums) to the user you wish to send your e-mail address to).

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. TranceAddict **™** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Contests**

Our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used [shared with the contest [survey] sponsors] to notify the winners and award prizes. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend?s name and email address. TranceAddict **™** will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. TranceAddict **™** stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email (to prevent duplication and spam abuse). The friend may contact TranceAddict **™** at [http://www.tranceaddict.com/contact.php ](http://www.tranceaddict.com/contact.php) to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Google Ads / Reporting**

We use Google Analytics software to help give us insight as to who our visitors are - we also utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. TranceAddict and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.

Many sites on the net use this reporting tool - if you would like to opt-out please visit https://google.com/settings and follow the instructions.

**Sharing Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users? personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Link Theft** We do not condone direct link(s) to digital media and other large files on external web/ftp sites on the TranceAddict.com forums. Please link to the originating source and have respect for other webmasters and the time they put in to maintain their pages. Alternatively, it is also not acceptable to post direct links to files on our TranceAddict.com servers - please direct all links to www.tranceaddict.com instead. 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [http://www.tranceaddict.com/feedback.shtml ](http://www.tranceaddict.com/feedback.shtml)

**Last Modified:** March 28th 2014
